are already houses welcome back and in this video I'm going to show you how to
已经 欢迎回到家里了 这个视频我将告诉你 如何
sort custom objects by any attribute that you want so let's go ahead and say
按任何属性排序自定义对象 你想要的，让我们继续说吧
that you were working on the social network and you had a bunch of users signed up and they all had like first
你正在 从事 社交活动 网络， 你有一堆 用户 报名参加，他们都是第一个
names last names birthdays maybe a user ID
名字姓氏生日也许是用户 ID
they also listed their favorite colors and I don't know like how much money was
他们还列出了自己喜欢的颜色 我不知道像多少钱 了
in their bank account for whatever reason many ways these users had a bunch
在他们的银行账户中 理由是这些用户有很多方式
of different attributes and you were having a tough time figuring out how to
不同的属性 ， 你是 我很难搞清楚如何 做到这一点
make an algorithm or function to sort by each one so let's say you want to sort
制作一个算法或函数来排序 每 一个让我们说你想要 排序
by favorite colors or birthdays you can do that so check this out what we're
通过喜欢的颜色或生日，你可以 这样做所以检查 了这一点正是我们
going to do is just like before we're going to use operator module and we're
要做的就像我们之前一样 我将使用运营商模块
going to import attribute getter so now item getter by attribute getter so now
现在要去导入属性getter 现在，属性getter的项目getter
let me go ahead and make a real quick class and I think you need two spaces
让我继续 前进，做 一个真正的快速 我 觉得你需要两个空格
Pepe all right so class user and let me just make dunder init and we'll say that
Pepe 好吧所以上课的用户让我 只是让dunder init和我们说 ，
whenever you make a new user object we'll say that they need a name and user
每当你创建一个新的用户对象 我们会说他们需要一个名字 和用户
ID so we'll just say x and y all right so self name equals x and so I'll just
ID所以我们只是说x和y 都可以 所以自我名称等于x，所以我只是
name it a user ID equals y so whenever we initialize object we'll just say like
将其命名为用户ID等于y，所以每当 我们初始化对象，我们只会说
Bucky ten or whatever so something like that all right looking good now actually another thing that I want to do I'll
巴基十个或任何 所以像 所有的权利 看起来不错 现在居然 我要做的另一件事我会做
show you guys a cool it's not really a trick but dunder init of course that means whenever you initialize there's
向你们展示一个很酷的 它并不是真的 诀窍但当然是 dunder init 意味着每当你初始化那里
another one called ar e PR so this is a string representation of this object so
另外一个叫ARËPR，所以这是一个 这个对象的字符串表示如此
that means let's say that you just wanted to print out let's say that you
这意味着让我们说你 就是 想打印出来让我们说你
had um an instance of this user class that was Bucky
有一个这个用户类的实例 那是巴基
so the info was just the name Bucky and my user ID which was ten but then later
所以信息只是Bucky 和 我的用户ID是十，但 后来
on in your code you just said print out Bucky well then Python would be like
在你的代码中你刚才 说打印出来 Bucky然后Python 就好了
what exactly do you want me to print out a about him his name or his user ID or
你究竟想要 我 打印出来的是什么？ 关于他的姓名或他的用户ID 或
his name and his user ID or do you want to print out where that object is in
他的名字和他的用户名或你想要的 打印出该对象所在的位置
memory I mean what the heck am I supposed to know what Bucky is what you
记忆 我的意思是我到底是什么 应该知道Bucky是什么
want well that's what this is for right here so what we can do is we can
我希望这 就是正确的 在这里，我们能做的就是我们能做到的
basically just return whatever representation we want to make and we
基本上只是回报什么 我们想做的代表和我们
can make this however we want so I'll say whenever I just say print out Bucky
可以做到这一点，但我们想要，所以我会 每当我说打出Bucky时就说
then it's going to print out that object's name and then I'll print out
然后它会打印出来 对象的名字 ，然后我打印 出来
his ID and I'll separate them by like I don't know semicolons or whatever so
他的身份证，我会 像我一样 将 他们分开 不知道分号或其他什么
plus and again this user ID it's actually going to be um an int so we
再加上这个用户ID吧 实际上将是一个int所以我们
need to make sure to convert that to a string sofie's your ID and the name of
需要确保 将其转换成 一个 串SOFIE是你的ID和 名称
course is already a string so that's why we don't need to do that but again
当然已经 是一个字符串所以 这就是原因 我们不需要再这样做了
whenever we say print out an instance or a user object then this is what it's going to give us so just save us a
每当我们说打印出一个实例或 一个用户对象， 那就是它的本质 要给我们这么拯救我们一个
little bit of time from formatting everyone later on all right so now let
格式化的一点点时间 所有人以后都可以，所以现在让
me go ahead and make a bunch of users paste that in so you guys don't have to
我继续 前进 ，使一群用户 粘贴在这样你们 就不必
watch me do it all so now I have a list of user objects I have Bucky
看我 做 的 这 一切 ，现在我有一个列表 用户对象 我有Bucky
Sally tuna Brian who's name is tuna that's weird but actually that would be
莎莉金枪鱼布莱恩谁的名字是金枪鱼 这很奇怪但实际上会是这样
a pretty cool name I'm gonna name my kid tuna all right and they all have user
一个非常酷的名字， 我会给我的 孩子起个名字 金枪鱼没事，他们都有用户
IDs nothing special however what we want to do is we pretty much just want to sort all of these
ID 没什么特别的 但是我们想做的就是我们漂亮 我只是想对所有 这些 进行排序
users so let's see what order they're sorted in by default so for user in
用户让我们看看他们的订单 默认排序，以便用户进入
users just go ahead and print user so run that and check it out and again it
用户只需继续打印用户即可 运行它并再次检查 它
prints it and maybe if I add a space right there might be a little bit easier
打印它，也许如果我添加一个空格 对，可能会有 一点点 容易
to see but again it prints it in the specified order so by default and see
再次看到 它打印出来的 指定的顺序所以默认 看看
what's going on here prints out Bucky Sally tuna Brian re so it prints it out
这里发生了什么打印出Bucky 莎莉金枪鱼布莱恩重新打印出来
in whatever order we initialize objects in however we want to you know make
无论我们初始化对象的顺序如何 但是我们想要你知道make
special functions to sort them by name and also the
按名称对它们进行排序的特殊功能 并且还
our ID since whenever like you're looking for a friend you just don't want
我们的ID就像你一样 寻找你 不想要 的朋友
to look through all of them randomly randomly wouldn't be very efficient so
随机 浏览 所有这些 随机不会那么高效
check this out let me add that little separator so they
看一下这个 让我添加那个小分隔符，以便它们
don't cut it all jumbled together and we'll do this for user just name it user
不要把它们全部混杂在一起 我们将为用户命名用户
still in sorted and again what do you want to sort users nothing new there
仍然在排序，你又是什么 想要在那里对用户进行排序
but what we're going to do is we just don't want to sort it in the default
但我们要做的就是我们 不想 在默认情况下对其 进行 排序
order what we want to do is we want to sort it by we'll say sort them by name
订购 我们想要做的是我们想要的 排序它通过 我们会按名称排序说出来
first so get an attribute and in this case we'll just type name and this is
首先得到一个属性，并在此 我们只需输入名称，这就是
how we can specify how to sort so just like before we'll print user and check
我们如何才能指定如何进行排序 就像之前 我们打印用户并检查一样
this out so again what this does is it just doesn't print them out in default
这样做又是什么呢 只是不 默认 打印 出来
order it sorts them by their name and then this is a lot more efficient and again if you want to do by ID
责令 他们的名字 它们排序， 并 那么这个效率要高得多 再次， 如果你想通过ID做
then what I just name it user ID then we'll just say sort this iterable by
然后， 我只是将其 命名为用户ID 我们只是说这个可迭代的排序
this attribute so now we can go ahead and run this and check it out so this is
这个属性 现在我们可以继续 并 运行它并检查出来，这是
default this one sorted by name and this of course is sorted by their user ID two
默认这个按名称排序，这个 当然按用户ID 2排序
five nine forty three sixty one and 77 so how awesome is that again a lot
五九四十三 六十一和77 所以这又 是多么令人敬畏
easier than you may have been doing it before oh yeah there you go in six minutes you learn not only about
比你可能做的更容易 在哦，是的，你进去六点 几分钟你不仅要学习
representations about how to sort custom objects I mean this is absolutely fantastic so think as watching I will
关于如何对自定义进行排序的表示 对象我的意思是绝对的 太棒了所以想想看我会的
smell you next time
下次闻你